optionow.com 2013-06-22

# Security and Privacy

## Privacy Policy

## No matter if you are a former or an existing client or just a visitor on our website, the privacy of our users is one of Clever Invest Label Management ltd.’s main concerns, therefore Clever Invest Label Management ltd. is committed to safeguard all personal information collected from our valued clients.

By providing Clever Invest Label Management ltd. With your personal information such as Full Name, Mailing Address, ID number, Passport Number etc., you are providing Clever Invest Label Management ltd. with full consent to gather, utilize, store and protect the information provided in the manner described below.

## **When is Information Collected from** Clever Invest Label Management ltd. **‘s Clients:**

  * When opening a Live/Demo trading account with Clever Invest Label Management ltd. (When filling in electronic registration forms).
  * When funding your personal trading account.
  * When withdrawing from your personal trading account.
  * Personal Information such as Full Name, Address, Date of Birth, ID Number and Occupation
  * Financial Information such as assets, investment experience and monthly income, in order to evaluate your trading experience
  * When funding your account or withdrawing from your account, we may request documents such as a copy of an ID Document, Utility Bills and a Bank Statement

## **The Personal Information that may be Collected Includes:**

The above information collected from clients, helps Clever Invest Label Management ltd. understand your financial needs, provide you with products and services suitable to your needs, process your account transactions in a timely manner as well as provide you with the highest level of customer support.

## **How is information collected from** Clever Invest Label Management ltd.’s **Clients:** ****

Clients willingly provide Clever Invest Label Management ltd. with the personal information collected in the following ways:

  * On Completion of Electronic registration forms placed on the Clever Invest Label Management ltd Website or on a Clever Invest Label Management ltd Minisite.
  * When funding or withdrawing from trading accounts, clients voluntarily provide required documents
  * When trading on the Clever Invest Label Management ltd system
  * When contacting Clever Invest Label Management ltd or responding to a promotion advertised

There is certain information that is indirectly collected by Clever Invest Label Management ltd such as: IP Address, operating system, software configuration and the use of cookies.

## **What is the use of information collected by** Clever Invest Label Management ltd **:** ****

Clever Invest Label Management ltd will utilize the information collected from clients for the following purposes:

  * To verify clients identity
  * To set up, maintain and manage clients’ personal trading account
  * To process deposits and withdraws in clients’ personal trading account
  * To keep clients up to date with news, updates and new promotions at Clever Invest Label Management ltd
  * To analyze client activity in order to improve and provide clients with the best products and services
  * To provide clients with top quality customer support

## **The Sharing of Clients Personal Information:** ****

Clever Invest Label Management ltd  does not share any client information with any affiliated or unaffiliated 3rd parties and only under the below circumstances will  client’s personal information be shared:

  * In order to open, operate and service your personal trading account, Clever Invest Label Management ltd. may share information with service providers such as attorneys, accountants, auditors, and other financial professionals
  * In order to protect against fraud, money laundering, unauthorized transactions, claims or other liabilities, or by instruction of an applicable authority.
  * Income, credit history, net worth, or income information, will not be shared by Clever Invest Label Management ltd. under no circumstances
  * The company may share information with affiliates and introducing brokers, mainly for the calculation of these entity’s compensation

## **How does** Clever Invest Label Management ltd **  Protect the Information you Provide:** ****

Right on top of the Clever Invest Label Management ltd.’s priority list is  client’s security; therefore Clever Invest Label Management ltd takes all the necessary steps to make sure that your data is safe with us.

  * Clever Invest Label Management ltd uses the top notch data security technology, firewalls and data encryption
  * Every client owns his own personal user name and password which he uses to access Clever Invest Label Management ltd systems
  * All client information at Clever Invest Label Management ltd is restricted to a small group of management and employers that need to use this information

## **Links found on the** Clever Invest Label Management ltd **Website:** ****

Links to external sites may be found on the Clever Invest Label Management ltd website. Clever Invest Label Management ltd takes no responsibility for the content on the external websites and  advice to all clients to read the privacy policy of the external websites before leaving any personal information. The Clever Invest Label Management ltd Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by Clever Invest Label Management ltd.

## **Questions, Concerns or Complaints:** ****

If you have any questions, concerns or complaints, please don’t hesitate to contact us via phone, email or chat. Clever Invest Label Management ltd offers customer support in over 10 different languages.
